What? You think I didn't notice
that you're making moves
on my daughter?
You're even sucking up to me!
So, may the best man win.
You're ruining my move!
Well, I'm just trying
to patch things up with Joey.
That's why we're here,
hiding from the syndicate.
Where are you going again?
If you don't want me to go out,
then you buy what I need.
I have this fear...
that I'll lose you someday.
Do we have enemies here?
Yes, those three fools!
Good thing we're okay now,
right?
I hope it's always like this.
Like we don't have problems.
What are you doing here?
We only have one problem.
What is it this time?
The one you told us to watch
seems to be plotting something.
If she tries,
I'll kill her myself.
You'll kill someone?
It was just an expression.
Tomas, be careful
with what you say.
Can you just let it go?
And don't ever dictate to me!
What happened to
the one Cruz spoke with?
Can't be contacted anymore.
Did Cruz identify
who called the hotline?
- [SCREAMS]
- Liza De Leon.
I hope you're right, Jin Ho.
I don't know when,
I don't know where.
But I'm sure
of my feelings for you.
I love you, Joey.
[OBB]
What?
But when I confessed to you...
Yes, I know.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey, I'm...
I'm sorry, I hurt you,
I know.
I thought we couldn't work.
That it was impossible...
because you're young,
we're different.
I know I hurt you,
and I'm sorry.
I'll make it up to you, please.
We're okay now, right?
Why are you complicating things?
Joey, I'm just being honest
with you now.
What do you want me to say?
That we're okay?
That we can be a couple?
Didn't you reject me
when I confessed before?
And I accepted that.
I moved on.
And now you're telling me
you love me?
It feels like
you're playing with my feelings.
Joey, it's not like that.
That's not what I wanted
to happen.
But that's what I feel.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Joey!
- [WHIP WHACKS]
- Enough! Enough!
- [GROANS AND BAWLS]
You snake!
[GROANING]
Enough!
[BAWLS]
- [WHIP WHACKS]
- [GROANS AND BAWLS]
Enough!
Enough! Enough, Berdugo! Enough!
Please, have mercy, enough!
You think you can fool us, huh.
We know your plans!
Stop it...
Please, have mercy, stop it.
Let me go.
I didn't do anything.
What are you talking about?
I didn't do anything!
That's what a guilty person
usually says.
[SOBBING]
I saw your phone.
But we just wanted to make sure
you won't carry out your plans!
So? Is that ready?
Make sure Liza's car
doesn't stop, okay?
Yes, Boss.
Berdugo, enough.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHINES]
Honestly...
I told Matias
maybe his suspicion was wrong.
That's why I need proof.
I said, if Liza leaves,
it means she'll betray us.
It was a test...
of loyalty.
Have mercy, Berdugo.
And you failed!
You know what happens
to those who betray me, right?
Enough...
I didn't do anything.
Let me go.
Please have mercy!
Please, help me!
Okay, Chief, I'll call later.
So, Oppa? Are you okay?
Joey, wait, wait.
Ah...
Dad, what's happening?
Liza was supposed to surrender.
But she didn't show up.
So, Jin Ho is worried.
Why would he worry?
Something bad
must have happened to her.
That's why she didn't show up.
I know where she might be.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir...
I want to help you find Berdugo.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BRAZEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yes, I got the location map.
Thank you.
[BRAZEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
Probably there.
This place looks big.
That's the only place I know
since they don't trust me much.
That means your group
doesn't accept you.
But we'll still try.
I'll just call Chief.
You're already excluded there,
why join them?
We're here, your friends.
He's doing it for Liza.
Because if you love someone,
you're willing to take a risk.
I wanted to protect Liza
and you guys too.
That's why I stayed.
Do you really have
to talk to her like that?
He's already stressed.
Joey! Oppa!
Do you and Joey have a problem?
None.
- [WHIP WHACKS]
- [GROANS AND BAWLS]
Enough!
- [WHIP WHACKS]
- [GROANS AND BAWLS]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
We're done talking, Liza.
You can't be trusted!
Whatever you say,
consider it your last words!
I helped grow this organization.
I brought millions!
Why would I do that to you!
Why would I betray you?
Enough, Berdugo.
Please, have mercy.
Don't hurt me anymore, please.
- Please, have mercy.
- Fine.
I won't hurt you anymore.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WHIP WHACKS]
- [GROANS AND BAWLS]
Joey, Joey, teka.
We have nothing else
to talk about now
but our friend's situation.
So please don't bring up
wanting us to be together.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You got great timing.
Jin Ho...
Look. I'm sorry for
what I said earlier.
Are you okay, Jin Ho?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho, don't lose hope.
Just trust, Jin Ho.
I'm sure dad will help too.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
We need help.
The place is big.
There's a lot to guard.
We need to verify
this info first.
But I'll coordinate
with other precincts,
maybe they can send their men.
Chief, can I take a break first?
Why?
I've been through
a lot with this person.
I want to be the one
to catch him myself.
All right, I'll send Cruz there.
- Salazar.
- Sir?
Call Cruz.
Tell him to come to my office.
Yes, Sir.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Matias, since
you'll handle operations
both in and out,
I want everything in order.
I'll take care of it, Berdugo.
Good.
We need to recover...
because we've lost a lot.
I thought of canceling
our meeting
with our client, Mr. Stuart.
Why?
He's one of our top clients.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
That's the problem,
we're in the hot seat right now.
They might lose trust
if they see we're careless.
There's a bigger chance
they'll back out
if they find out...
we don't control the situation.
So, where will you
hold the meeting?
The radar's still hot.
Don't cancel.
I have a plan.
Cruz will go with you
while I'm gone.
Whatever he says, follow it.
Clear?
Sir, yes, Sir!
Major, will we be here for long?
Well, hopefully, with the info
we got from Jin Ho,
this will all end.
Dad, Jin Ho
and I are begging you,
if you see Liza,
please don't hurt her.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho, that's also what my
daughter told me when...
we caught you,
not to hurt you.
Joey, thank you.
Don't worry, I'll do everything
to keep her safe.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, Sir.
Now I know why Joey
is always positive.
She got it from you.
Take care.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry.
You really scared me.
You really did.
I know.
I've just been
really stressed lately.
And I think you should
take a break
if it's affecting you.
You know, it's just work.
You're right.
I have an idea.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
You're right,
I should detach from work
even for a while.
And I think the foundation's
groundbreaking event
is the best outlet.
Really?
You'll attend tomorrow?
Yes.
Of course, I want to support
my wife.
And I think this is
the perfect opportunity
for the foundation.
so I want to be there
for my wife.
Thank you, Hon.
Well, I'll prepare
what I'll wear.
Ah, where will you
hold this event?
Ah, at the old prairie.
We bought part
of the land there.
With enough donations
and sponsorship,
we'll build the orphanage there.
Well, I'm sure
it will be a success.
Thank you, Hon.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh...
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Miguel...
you scared me.
I'm sorry.
But wait, what are you
doing here?
Weren't you with Joey?
You were safe in hiding,
why did you leave?
Did you abandon her?
Don't worry, Cruz is there.
They're safe.
The Korean gave a tip,
that's why I left.
And I want to make sure
we'll be safe
once the syndicate is gone.
And when that happens,
you won't have
to be afraid anymore.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, Joey...
you woke up early,
coffee?
Good morning po.
It's okay, later.
Did dad call already?
Not yet, but I'm sure
Chief is working on it now.
Stay alert.
If you see anything strange,
tell me right away.
Yes, Sir!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Turn right there.
Check, maybe
the warehouse is there.
Okay, Sir!
Did Mr. Stuart confirm?
Yes, Berdugo.
He even seemed pleased.
He said the meeting place
felt like a movie set.
That's good.
We need to please our clients.
Is she still alive?
Yes, Berdugo.
Don't worry, Liza.
I won't prolong your suffering.
Take her with you.
We'll dispose of her
along the way.
Go on, carry her now.
Good morning.
Good morning, Joey.
Is Jin Ho still asleep?
He's not in his room.
Actually, we thought
he was with you.
What?
Then where is he?
Let's find Jin Ho!
- Check upstairs.
- Wait, I'll check upstairs.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [PETER SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
- Jin Ho!
Jin Ho!
[PETER SHOUTING]
- Nothing, he's not there.
- Jin Ho!
- Not there?
- Not there.
- Jin Ho!
- Huh?
- Not there?
- He's not there.
Let's find him, quick!
- Outside, come on!
- Jin Ho!
Jin Ho!
Isn't there a guard here?
Gonzalo was stationed here.
His motorcycle is gone too.
Help!
Gonzalo, what happened here?
Sir, the Korean escaped.
He even took my gun.
[REVVING]
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm coming for you, Liza.
[REVVING]
Thank you.
I'm sure he'll go to Liza.
Let's go.
Major Delgado told me
when I spoke to him,
I should take you home.
Peter, you stay
with Major for now.
But what now? We don't know...
what will happen to Jin Ho.
Let's just hope he is okay.
Where could he have gone?
Did Oppa escape again?
I don't think so.
I think he's looking for Liza.
Come on, get in.
We might catch Jin Ho
on the way.
Let's go, let's go.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Follow that car.
Yes, Sir!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Where are we taking Liza,
Berdugo?
Anywhere deserted we pass by.
Hurry...
I still have an event to attend.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
What's the place
Jin Ho mentioned?
It could be anywhere.
This area is huge.
Maybe we'll see him here.
We might even run into him.
We're following a subject now.
Possible target.
That's Dad.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Get ready.
We'll block them.
Yes, Sir!
Who are they following?
Could it be Jin Ho?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Move!
Hurry!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN COCKING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
The Hope Circle Foundation
will be able to build
the Angel Sanctuary.
We would like to thank
all of you so much.
Jin Ho, we're worried about you.
I can't go there right now.
What matters is
I get to the quarry.
Berdugo might be there.
Someone told us the group
we're looking for is here.
- Jin Ho!
- Berdugo!
This day won't end
without us catching Berdugo.
Surrender now!
I'll give you ten seconds!
I'm out of bullets, Berdugo.
We have no choice.